<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: peru | images and words]]></title>
  <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/blog/categories/peru/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/"/>
  <updated>2013-09-18T20:52:21+10:00</updated>
  <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ryan Boucher]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young boy in boat]]></title>
    <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/young-boy-in-boat"/>
    <updated>2013-06-06T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/puzzle</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!-- ![Iquitos](http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2856/9782423795_9089a9a32c_k.jpg) -->

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iquitos]]></title>
    <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/iquitos"/>
    <updated>2013-06-05T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/improve-this</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/peru/iquitos.jpg" alt="Iquitos" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arequipa]]></title>
    <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/arequipa"/>
    <updated>2013-06-04T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/the-king-is-dead</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/peru/arequipa.jpg" alt="Arequipa" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machu Pichu]]></title>
    <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/machu-pichu"/>
    <updated>2013-06-03T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/big-data</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:center;"><img src="/images/peru/inka.jpg" alt="derp" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Thoughts]]></title>
    <link href="www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/first-thoughts"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T00:00:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>www.distributedlife.com/travel/peru/dark-matter</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After barely pausing for customs I was promptly asked if I wanted to buy a CD of The Rolling Stones latest album. It&rsquo;s still in it&rsquo;s plastic wrapper he assured me. I let him know that I didn&rsquo;t have anything to play it. He seemed to remember that iPods existed and wandered off.</p>

<p class="image"><span class="portrait"><img src="www.distributedlife.com/travel/images/peru/lima.jpg" alt="Statue with Graphitti in Lima"></span></p>


<p>I met up with Sarah and Dan, Scotty&rsquo;s friends who were happy to guide me around. I wasn&rsquo;t sure what I would make of LA. Venice beach reminds me Bondi beach with just a bit more tacky stuff. The rest of it doesn&rsquo;t feel distinct in anyway. I did stay away from the hollywood sections apart from a quick drive through it. I did manage to experience what I come to do, and that was to eat tacos worth eating. They were delicious. I also learnt that in LA ordering from road side food vans is not necessarily a bad thing, and probably wont kill you, a stark contrast from home.</p>

<blockquote><p>“I find the baño and like the others on this trek, it&rsquo;s a real tuck your trousers into your socks place.”</p></blockquote>

<p>I arrived in Lima and brushed off every taxi driver before being told that bus doesn&rsquo;t run to the airport any more. The taxi trip was an true experience, full pelt, peculiar road choices (I checked his route as we drove on my own map), the stupendous amounts of traffic and merging sections that take one seething mass of cars and turn them into a slightly narrower seething mass. I wish I recorded the video. I&rsquo;ll try recording it on the way home. The trip also gave me a look into how Lima could have been. We drive past a sign, LIMA in big bold letters, grass fills the islands between the two lanes, trees line the edge. The road stretches on, the grass is pale and not looked after. The trees don&rsquo;t exist. One side of the road is the Rio Rimac and poor adobe dwellings, the other side are slightly better houses, the shift in quality is easily distinguishable as the house have been completed.</p>

<p class="image"><span class="landscape"><img src="www.distributedlife.com/travel/images/peru/cusco.jpg" alt="Statue with Graphitti in Lima"></span></p>


<p>I get dropped off at the main plaza. It&rsquo;s 830 in the morning, I sit on the steps in front of the cathedral and soak in the sounds of the city. The murmur of society, the hum of transport, the gentle honking of sonar-taxies. I am here.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
